[Music]
now Carlos you've been assigned to
travel with President Clinton as an
emissary for uh his wife's campaign now
how is that going Larry New Hampshire is
great coming up on the main stage our
sweetest girl
Splendor Jesus Carlos are you at a strip
club okay uh I think the establishment's
name is stilettos
uh but maybe it's a shoe store who am I
to judge if you win the nomination which
a lot of people hope that you do
right in in the general election even
though you don't understand this would
you promise to schlong Donald Trump just
say a lot of people are wondering like
uh who you're running potential
running would it be a you're looking for
a job is that it I uh well uh if you're
please get down on one knee uh
com